Abraham Ribicoff Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Senate Records, 1963-1980 (Box 22-616)
  - Administrative file (Box 22)
    - Connecticut file, 1969-1978 (Box 36)
      - Housing
        - 1971, Mar.-1974, July, (4 folders)
        - 1974, Sept.-1978, Jan., (7 folders) (Box 56)
        - 1978, Mar.-1980, Oct., (3 folders) (Box 57)
      - Conservation
        - 1970, Jan.-1971, June, (3 folders)
        - 1971, July, 1972, June, (5 folders) (Box 58)
        - 1972, July-1974, Apr., (7 folders) (Box 59)
        - 1974, May-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 60)
        - 1975, Jan.-1976, Oct., (9 folders) (Box 61)
        - 1976, Nov.-1977, Nov., (8 folders) (Box 62)
        - 1977, Dec.-1980, May, (8 folders) (Box 63)
      - Kilbourn, Orrin, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Motor vehicle and state police, (2 folders)
      - Energy
        - 1977, Jan.-1978, Mar.
        - 1978, Apr.-1980, Nov., (5 folders) (Box 65)
      - Economic development
        - 1974, May-1977, June, (3 folders)
        - 1977, July-1980, July, (7 folders) (Box 66)
      - Consumer problems
        - 1977, Jan.-July, (3 folders)
        - 1977, Aug.-1979, Dec., (8 folders) (Box 67)
        - 1979, Nov.-1980, Mar. (Box 68)
      - Miscellany
        - 1969, Sept.-1970, May, (7 folders)
        - 1970, June-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 69)
        - 1970, Nov.-1971, Apr., (8 folders) (Box 70)
        - 1971, May-Nov., (7 folders) (Box 71)
        - 1971, Dec.-1972, June, (9 folders) (Box 72)
        - 1972, July-1973, Jan., (8 folders) (Box 73)
        - 1973, Feb.-Sept., (9 folders) (Box 74)
        - 1973, Sept.-1974, Mar., (10 folders) (Box 75)
        - 1974, Apr.-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 76)
        - 1974 (Box 77)
        - 1974, Nov.-1975, Apr., (9 folders) (Box 78)
        - 1975, May-Sept., (9 folders) (Box 79)
        - 1975, Oct.-1976, Mar., (9 folders) (Box 80)
        - 1976, Apr.-Aug., (8 folders) (Box 81)
        - 1976, Sept.-1977, Jan., (7 folders) (Box 82)
        - 1977 (Box 83)
          - Feb.-June, (10 folders)
          - July-Nov., (8 folders) (Box 84)
        - 1977, Dec.-1978, May, (10 folders) (Box 85)
        - 1978, June-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 86)
        - 1979, Jan.-1980, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 87)
        - 1980 (Box 88)
    - Newsletter
      - 1965-1974, (7 folders)
      - 1974-1975, (10 folders) (Box 89)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
    - "All to the Good" (newspaper column)
      - 1963, May-1965, May, (11 folders)
      - 1965, May-1966, Sept., (36 folders) (Box 90)
      - 1966, Oct.-1968, July, (43 folders) (Box 91)
      - 1969, Feb.-1970, July, (40 folders) (Box 92)
      - 1970-1974, July, (40 folders) (Box 93)
    - Speeches and releases (Box 94)
      - 1963, Jan.-June, (61 folders)
      - 1963, July-Oct., (37 folders) (Box 95)
      - 1963-1964, Oct., (16 folders) (Box 96)
      - 1964 (Box 97)
        - Jan.-May, (45 folders)
        - May-Oct., (32 folders) (Box 98)
      - 1964, Oct.-1965, Mar., (22 folders) (Box 99)
      - 1965 (Box 100)
        - Apr.-May, (12 folders)
        - May-Nov., (18 folders) (Box 101)
      - 1966 (Box 102)
        - Jan.-Feb., (34 folders)
        - Feb.-Apr., (21 folders) (Box 103)
        - Apr.-May, (28 folders) (Box 104)
        - May-Aug., (40 folders) (Box 105)
        - Aug.-Dec., (40 folders) (Box 106)
      - 1967 (Box 107)
        - Jan.-Mar., (25 folders)
        - Mar.-May, (32 folders) (Box 108)
        - May-June, (46 folders) (Box 109)
        - June-Sept., (39 folders) (Box 110)
        - Sept.-Oct., (43 folders) (Box 111)
      - 1967, Nov.-1968, Mar., (51 folders) (Box 112)
      - 1968 (Box 113)
        - Mar.-May, (52 folders)
        - June-Aug., (55 folders) (Box 114)
        - Aug.-Sept., (44 folders) (Box 115)
        - Sept.-Oct., (47 folders) (Box 116)
      - 1968, Oct.-1969, (43 folders) (Box 117)
      - 1969 (Box 118)
        - Jan.-May, (62 folders)
        - May-July, (44 folders) (Box 119)
        - Aug.-Dec., (69 folders) (Box 120)
      - 1969, Dec.-1970, Mar., (53 folders) (Box 121)
      - 1970 (Box 122)
        - Mar.-May, (40 folders)
        - May-July, (40 folders) (Box 123)
        - July-Sept., (42 folders) (Box 124)
        - Sept.-Nov., (44 folders) (Box 125)
      - 1970, Nov.-1971, Mar., (55 folders) (Box 126)
      - 1971 (Box 127)
        - Mar.-June, (54 folders)
        - June-Oct., (61 folders) (Box 128)
        - Oct.-Nov., (49 folders) (Box 129)
      - 1971, Nov.-1972, Feb., (60 folders) (Box 130)
      - 1972 (Box 131)
        - Feb.-May, (57 folders)
        - May-Aug., (53 folders) (Box 132)
        - Aug.-Dec., (63 folders) (Box 133)
      - 1972, July-1973, Jan., (34 folders) (Box 134)
      - 1973 (Box 135)
        - Jan.-Mar., (36 folders)
        - Mar.-Apr., (41 folders) (Box 136)
        - May-July, (55 folders) (Box 137)
        - Aug.-Oct., (46 folders) (Box 138)
        - Nov.-Dec., (52 folders) (Box 139)
      - 1974 (Box 140)
        - Jan.-Mar., (46 folders)
        - Apr.-July, (51 folders) (Box 141)
        - Aug.-Dec., (66 folders) (Box 142)
      - 1975 (Box 143)
        - Jan.-May, (67 folders)
        - June-Dec., (62 folders) (Box 144)
      - 1976
        - Jan.-May, (58 folders) (Box 145)
        - June-Dec., (55 folders) (Box 146)
      - 1977 (Box 147)
        - Jan.-Apr., (50 folders)
        - May-Sept., (45 folders) (Box 148)
        - Oct.-Dec., (30 folders) (Box 149)
      - 1978 (Box 150)
        - Jan.-June, (69 folders)
        - July-Dec., (80 folders) (Box 151)
      - 1979 (Box 152)
        - Jan.-June, (59 folders)
        - July-Dec., (54 folders) (Box 153)
      - 1980 (Box 154)
        - Jan.-May, (38 folders)
        - June-Oct., (38 folders) (Box 155)
        - Nov.-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 156)
    - Releases phoned or not printed
      - 1966, June-1977, Sept., (7 folders)
      - 1969, Jan.-1979, July, (8 folders) (Box 157)
    - Radio-TV correspondence (Box 158)
      - 1962, Dec.-1963, Aug., (10 folders)
      - 1963, Sept.-1964, Mar., (10 folders) (Box 159)
      - 1964, Apr.-1965, Mar., (13 folders) (Box 160)
      - 1965, Apr.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 161)
      - 1966, (13 folders) (Box 162)
      - 1967, Jan.-Oct., (5 folders) (Box 163)
      - 1967, Nov.-1968, Dec., (13 folders) (Box 164)
      - 1969, Jan.-1970, Dec., (2 folders) (Box 165)
      - 1971, July-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 166)
      - 1972 (Box 167)
      - 1973, (3 folders) (Box 168)
      - 1975, (3 folders) (Box 169)
      - 1976, (4 folders) (Box 170)
      - 1977-1978, Jan., (6 folders) (Box 171)
      - 1978-1980, (7 folders) (Box 172)
    - Important statements, 1977-1980, (4 folders) (Box 173)
    - Radio-TV broadcasts
      - 1965, (4 folders)
      - 1965, Jan.-1966, June, (5 folders) (Box 174)
      - 1966, Jan.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 175)
      - 1967-1968, (6 folders) (Box 176)
      - 1969, Jan.-1972, Dec., (17 folders) (Box 177)
      - 1972, Jan.-1974, Aug., (15 folders) (Box 178)
      - 1975, Jan.-1977, Dec., (28 folders) (Box 179)
      - 1978, Feb.-1980, June, (4 folders) (Box 180)
    - Thank-you letters
      - 1968, Feb.-1969, Aug., (2 folders)
      - 1969, Dec.-1972, Apr., (8 folders) (Box 181)
      - 1972, May-1973, Sept., (8 folders) (Box 182)
      - 1973, Oct.-1974, Oct., (9 folders) (Box 183)
      - 1974, Nov.-1975, Aug., (7 folders) (Box 184)
      - 1975, Sept. 1976, Sept., (7 folders) (Box 185)
      - 1976, Oct.-1977, Sept., (10 folders) (Box 186)
      - 1977, Oct.-1978, Sept., (10 folders) (Box 187)
      - 1978, Oct.-1979, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 188)
      - 1980 (Box 189)
    - Incoming letters
      - 1967, Dec.-1972, Mar., (4 folders)
      - 1972, May-1976, June, (7 folders) (Box 190)
    - Very important correspondence, 1963, Nov.-1973, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 191)
  - Departmental file
    - American Bicentennial
      - 1972, Sept.-1975, Mar., (6 folders)
      - 1975, Apr.-1976, Sept., (6 folders) (Box 192)
    - Arms Control and Disarmament, 1966, Sept.-1976, Sept., (2 folders)
    - Atomic Energy Commission
      - 1964-1966, (2 folders)
      - 1966, Nov.-1980, June, (9 folders) (Box 193)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board
      - 1968, June-1980, Dec., (9 folders) (Box 194)
    - Commerce Department (Box 195)
      - 1966, Aug.-1967, Dec., (7 folders)
      - 1968, Feb.-1969, Dec., (9 folders) (Box 196)
      - 1970, Jan.-1973, Dec., (10 folders) (Box 197)
      - 1974, Jan.-1976, Aug., (8 folders) (Box 198)
      - 1976, Sept.-1978, May, (9 folders) (Box 199)
      - 1978, June-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 200)
    - Economic Development Administration
      - 1966, Mar.-1972, Apr., (7 folders)
      - 1972, May-1977, Jan., (8 folders) (Box 201)
      - 1977, Jan.-Sept., (9 folders) (Box 202)
      - 1977, Oct.-1980, Oct., (10 folders) (Box 203)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1968, June-1973, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 204)
    - Defense Department
      - Chronological file
        - 1966, Sept.-1972, Nov., (8 folders)
        - 1972, Dec.-1975, Apr., (9 folders) (Box 205)
        - 1975, May-1978, Dec., (10 folders) (Box 206)
        - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 207)
      - Defense contracts
        - 1970, May-1973, Feb., (3 folders)
        - 1973, Apr.-1974, July, (3 folders) (Box 208)
      - Air Force Department, 1973, Apr.-1980, Aug., (3 folders)
      - Army Department, 1972, Oct.-1980, (4 folders)
      - Army Corps of Engineers (Box 209)
        - 1963, Oct. 1972, (10 folders)
        - 1970, Jan.-1972, July, (9 folders) (Box 210)
        - 1972, Aug.-1975, Feb., (8 folders) (Box 211)
        - 1975, Mar.-1976, Mar., (7 folders) (Box 212)
        - 1976, Apr.-1977, Mar., (7 folders) (Box 213)
        - 1977, Apr.-1978, Mar., (7 folders) (Box 214)
        - 1978, Apr.-1979, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 215)
        - 1980, Jan.-Oct. (Box 216)
      - National Guard Bureau, 1979
      - Navy Department
        - 1971, Feb.-1978, May, (7 folders)
        - 1977, Oct.-1980, Oct., (6 folders) (Box 217)
      - Civil Defense, 1966, Nov.-1974, Dec., (2 folders) (Box 218)
      - Defense Supply Agency, 1974, Aug.
      - Connecticut defense industry, 1974, May
      - Calley, William, 1969, Nov.-1971, May, (7 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1977, Mar.-1979, May
    - District of Columbia, 1966, Sept.-1978, June, (5 folders) (Box 219)
    - Export-Import Bank, 1967, July-1978, June, (2 folders)
    - Federal Communications Commission
      - 1966, Sept.-1967, May, (2 folders)
      - 1967, June-1970, Sept. (Box 220)
      - 1970, Oct.-1973, Dec., (9 folders) (Box 221)
      - 1974, Jan.-1978, Dec., (10 folders) (Box 222)
      - 1978, Dec.-1980, July, (2 folders) (Box 223)
    - Federal Reserve Board, 1967, Jan.-1980, Oct., (5 folders)
    - Environmental Protection Agency
      - 1970, May-1971, May
      - 1971, June-1973, Dec., (9 folders) (Box 224)
      - 1974, Jan.-1975, June, (4 folders) (Box 225)
      - 1975, July-1977, June, (8 folders) (Box 226)
      - 1977, July-1978, Sept., (8 folders) (Box 227)
      - 1979, Oct.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 228)
      - 1980, Jan.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 229)
    - General Accounting Office
      - 1965, Dec.-1970, Aug., (3 folders)
      - 1970, Nov.-1980, Oct., (9 folders) (Box 230)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 231)
      - 1966, Aug.-1968, Aug., (2 folders)
      - 1968, Nov.-1976, Sept., (6 folders) (Box 232)
      - 1977, Apr.-1978, Dec., (2 folders) (Box 233)
      - 1978-1980, Mar., (3 folders) (Box 234)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare Department (Box 235)
      - Grants
        - 1974, Dec.-1976, Mar., (3 folders)
        - 1977, July-1980, June, (4 folders) (Box 236)
      - Health services and mental health, 1972, Dec.-1975, Aug., (2 folders)
      - Vocational rehabilitation (Box 237)
        - 1967, July-1973, Sept., (6 folders)
        - 1975, Oct.-1977, Feb., (2 folders) (Box 238)
      - Office of Education (Box 239)
        - 1967, Jan.-May
        - 1967, Nov.-1968, Dec. (Box 240)
        - 1968, Dec.-1969, Dec. (Box 241)
        - 1970, Jan.-1971, May, (3 folders) (Box 242)
        - 1971, June-Dec. (Box 243)
        - 1972, Jan.-July, (2 folders) (Box 244)
        - 1972, Sept.-1973, July, (2 folders) (Box 245)
        - 1974, Jan.-1975, Dec., (2 folders) (Box 246)
        - 1974 (Box 247)
        - 1975 (Box 248)
        - 1975 (Box 249)
        - 1976 (Box 250)
        - 1976 (Box 251)
        - 1977, Jan.-Aug. (Box 252)
        - 1978, Jan.-Aug. (Box 253)
        - 1978, Dec.-1980, Sept., (2 folders) (Box 254)
        - Miscellany (Box 255)
        - Miscellany (Box 256)
      - National Institutes of Health (Box 257)
        - Chronological file
          - 1966, Aug.-1972, June, (3 folders)
          - 1971, Dec.-1976, Nov., (3 folders) (Box 258)
          - 1977, Mar.-1980, Sept., (3 folders) (Box 259)
        - Correspondence, 1969, Feb.-1971, May, (2 folders)
      - Public Health Service (Box 260)
        - 1967, Jan.-1970, Mar., (3 folders)
        - 1969, Dec.-1971, June (Box 261)
        - 1971, Dec.-1972, May, (1 folder) (Box 262)
      - National Institutes of Mental Health, 1972, July-Aug.
      - Public Health Service (Box 263)
        - 1967, Dec.-1972, July, (3 folders)
        - 1972, Sept.-1975, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 264)
        - 1976, Jan.-1980, July, (5 folders) (Box 265)
        - Miscellany, (4 folders) (Box 266)
      - Social Security
        - 1966, Nov.-1974, Oct., (3 folders)
        - 1975, Apr.-1978, Apr., (2 folders) (Box 267)
      - Atomic Power Plants, 1964-1965
      - Cuban refugees
        - 1965-1968
        - 1968 (Box 268)
      - Jokl, Ernst, 1967
      - Medicare
        - 1966, Jan.-1968, Sept., (2 folders)
        - 1969, Nov.-1971, Aug., (3 folders) (Box 269)
        - 1971, Nov.-1974, Aug. (Box 270)
        - 1974, June, (2 folders) (Box 271)
        - 1975, July-1976, July (Box 272)
        - 1977, Jan.-1980, Oct., (4 folders) (Box 273)
      - Miscellany (Box 274)
        - 1967
        - 1968 (Box 275)
        - 1969 (Box 276)
        - 1969 (Box 277)
        - 1970 (Box 278)
        - 1970 (Box 279)
        - 1972 (Box 280)
        - 1973 (Box 281)
        - 1974 (Box 282)
        - 1975 (Box 283)
        - 1976 (Box 284)
        - 1976 (Box 285)
        - 1976 (Box 286)
        - 1978 (Box 287)
        - 1979 (Box 288)
        - 1980 (Box 289)
    - Housing and Urban Development
      - General
        - 1963, Aug.-1967, July, (4 folders)
        - 1967, Aug.-1968, Sept., (6 folders) (Box 290)
        - 1968, Oct.-1969, Aug., (9 folders) (Box 291)
        - 1969, Sept.-1970, Aug., (10 folders) (Box 292)
        - 1970, Sept.-1971, Mar., (8 folders) (Box 293)
        - 1971, Apr.-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 294)
        - 1972, Jan.-Sept., (8 folders) (Box 295)
        - 1972, Nov.-1973, July, (10 folders) (Box 296)
        - 1973, Aug.-1974, Apr., (8 folders) (Box 297)
        - 1974, May-Oct., (8 folders) (Box 298)
        - 1974, Nov.-1975, Oct., (7 folders) (Box 299)
        - 1975, Oct.-1976, Aug., (9 folders) (Box 300)
        - 1976, Sept.-1977, June, (8 folders) (Box 301)
        - 1977, July-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 302)
        - 1977, Dec.-1978, Apr., (10 folders) (Box 303)
        - 1978, May-Nov., (10 folders) (Box 304)
        - 1978, Dec.-1979, May, (6 folders) (Box 305)
        - 1979, June-Nov. (Box 306)
        - 1980, Jan.-Nov. (Box 307)
        - Special, 1978, July-Oct., (3 folders) (Box 308)
      - Community Facilities Administration
        - 1963, Mar.-1966, Aug., (4 folders)
        - 1966, Sept.-1968, Apr., (3 folders) (Box 309)
      - Federal Housing Administration, 1963, Jan.-1967, Nov., (3 folders)
      - Federal National Mortgage Association, 1968, Apr.-May
      - Public Housing Administration
        - 1963, Jan.-1967, Nov., (3 folders)
        - 1967, Apr.-1972, June, (6 folders) (Box 310)
      - Urban Renewal Administration
        - 1963, Feb.-1965, Nov., (2 folders)
        - 1966, Jan.-1967, Mar., (7 folders) (Box 311)
        - 1967, Mar.-1968, June, (8 folders) (Box 312)
        - 1968, Sept.-1970, May (Box 313)
      - Housing and Home Financing Agency
        - 1962, Dec.-1964, Oct., (4 folders)
    - Interior Department
      - General
        - 1963, June-1968, Dec., (3 folders)
        - 1968, Jan.-1970, June, (9 folders) (Box 314)
        - 1970, July-1974, Sept., (8 folders) (Box 315)
      - Fish and Wildlife Service
        - 1966, Dec.-1970, July, (2 folders)
        - 1973, June-1980, May, (2 folders) (Box 316)
      - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1966, Oct.-1980, Feb., (7 folders)
      - National Park Service (Box 317)
        - 1966, Nov.-1976, Nov., (10 folders)
        - 1977, Jan.-1980, June, (5 folders) (Box 318)
      - Bureau of Land Management, 1967, Sept.-1968, Mar.
      - Shepaug River, 1974, Mar.-1976, July
      - Bureau of Reclamation, 1968, Aug.
      - Office of Territories, 1966, Nov.-1968, Mar.
      - New England projects, 1963, July-1968, May (Box 319)
      - Federal Water Pollution Control Administration, 1965, Apr.-1970, Jan., (7 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box 320)
        - 1965, Mar.-1974, Mar., (9 folders)
        - 1974, Apr.-1978, July, (10 folders) (Box 321)
        - 1978, Aug.-1980, Sept., (5 folders) (Box 322)
    - Justice Department
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation
        - 1966, Sept.-1970, Dec., (3 folders)
        - 1971, Jan.-1980, May, (7 folders) (Box 323)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 324)
        - 1964, Mar.-1969, Mar., (6 folders)
        - 1969, Mar.-May, (10 folders) (Box 325)
        - 1969, June-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 326)
        - 1969, Dec.-1970, Mar., (9 folders) (Box 327)
        - 1970 (Box 328)
          - Mar.-July, (7 folders)
          - Aug.-Nov., (7 folders) (Box 329)
        - 1970, Dec.-1971, June, (8 folders) (Box 330)
        - 1971, June-1972, Jan., (9 folders) (Box 331)
        - 1972, Jan.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 332)
        - 1973, Jan.-May, (7 folders) (Box 333)
        - 1973, June-1974, Feb., (8 folders) (Box 334)
        - 1974, Feb.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 335)
        - 1975, Jan.-July, (7 folders) (Box 336)
        - 1975, Aug.-1976, Feb., (8 folders) (Box 337)
        - 1976 (Box 338)
          - Mar.-July, (8 folders)
          - July-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 339)
        - 1977, Jan.-June, (9 folders) (Box 340)
        - 1977, July-1978, Mar., (8 folders) (Box 341)
        - 1978, Apr.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 342)
        - 1979, (5 folders) (Box 343)
        - Soviet Jewry
        - Soviet Jewry (Box 344)
      - Bureau of Prisons
        - 1966, Nov.-1968, Apr., (2 folders)
        - 1968, May-1972, Nov., (7 folders) (Box 345)
        - 1973, Jan.-1976, Dec., (7 folders) (Box 346)
        - 1977, Jan.-1978, May, (8 folders) (Box 347)
        - 1978, June-1980, Nov., (6 folders) (Box 348)
      - Miscellany (Box 349)
        - 1965, June-1969, Apr., (11 folders)
        - 1969, May-1971, June, (10 folders) (Box 350)
        - 1971, July-1973, Mar., (11 folders) (Box 351)
        - 1973, Apr.-1975, Mar., (12 folders) (Box 352)
        - 1975, Apr.-1977, Nov., (12 folders) (Box 353)
        - 1977, Dec.-1980, Dec., (7 folders) (Box 354)
    - United States Postal Service, 1968, Mar.-1978, Sept., (5 folders) (Box 355)
    - Energy Department
      - Federal Power Commission
        - 1968, Feb.-1974, Nov., (3 folders)
        - 1972, Feb.-1977, Apr. (Box 356)
      - Federal Energy Administration
        - 1973, Apr.-1974, Feb., (6 folders)
        - 1974, Mar.-1977, Apr., (8 folders) (Box 357)
        - 1977, June-Nov. (Box 358)
      - Energy Research Development Administration, 1975, Dec.-1978, Dec., (5 folders)
      - Miscellany
        - 1977, Oct.-1978, Dec., (6 folders)
        - 1978, Nov.-1979, July (Box 359)
        - 1979, Oct.-1980, Nov. (Box 360)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1963, Jan.-1964, Sept., (2 folders)
    - Selective Service
      - 1969
    - State Department (Box 361)
      - Passports
      - Sahba kidnapping case
      - Bjorn, Douglas
      - Downey, John
      - Embassies
      - Visas
      - Miscellany
      - Miscellany (Box 362)
    - International Trade Commission
      - 1964, Apr.-1963, May, (5 folders)
      - 1973, Oct.-1979, Feb., (4 folders) (Box 363)
    - Transportation Department
      - Coast Guard
        - 1966, Oct.-1970, Feb., (5 folders)
        - 1970, Mar.-1976, Dec., (8 folders) (Box 364)
        - 1977, Jan.-1980, Oct., (4 folders) (Box 365)
        - 1967, Jan.-1969, Apr., (9 folders) (Box 366)
        - 1969, May-1972, June, (8 folders) (Box 367)
        - 1972, July-1977, Apr., (9 folders) (Box 368)
        - 1977, May-1980, Oct., (4 folders) (Box 369)
      - Federal Highway Administration
        - 1968, Nov.-1972, Apr., (3 folders)
        - 1972, May-1980, Jan., (7 folders) (Box 370)
      - Amtrak (Box 371)
        - 1971, Jan.-1974, July, (8 folders)
        - 1974, Aug.-1976, Dec., (4 folders) (Box 372)
      - Conrail
        - 1976, Apr.-1978, Aug., (4 folders)
        - 1978, Sept.-Dec. (Box 373)
      - Federal Railroad Administration, 1976, Dec.-1978, Dec., (5 folders)
      - Penn Central, 1972, Oct.-1975, July, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box 374)
        - 1967, Oct.-1972, Dec., (9 folders)
        - 1973, Jan.-1975, Mar., (8 folders) (Box 375)
        - 1975, Apr.-1979, Apr., (7 folders) (Box 376)
        - 1979, Nov.-1980, Sept., (2 folders) (Box 377)
        - 1980, (2 folders) (Box 378)
    - Treasury Department
      - Internal Revenue Service
        - 1973, June-1975, (2 folders)
        - 1975, July-Aug., (2 folders) (Box 379)
      - Office of Revenue Sharing, 1973, Dec.-1980, May, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany
        - 1966, Oct.-1967, Dec., (6 folders)
        - 1968, Jan.-1971, June, (7 folders) (Box 380)
        - 1971, Aug.-1974, Mar., (8 folders) (Box 381)
        - 1974, Apr.-1978, Apr., (13 folders) (Box 382)
        - 1978, May-1979, Dec., (4 folders) (Box 383)
    - United Nations
      - Human Rights Convention, 1963, Apr.-1968, Nov., (3 folders)
      - Red China, 1964, Mar.-1966, Nov., (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1967
        - Apr.-1968, Oct.
        - 1971, June-1980, Nov., (5 folders) (Box 384)
    - Veterans' Administration, 1967, Jan.-1980, Aug., (4 folders)
    - White House (Box 385)
      - President
        - 1963, Oct.-1966, Dec., (3 folders)
        - 1967, Jan.-1978, July, (11 folders) (Box 386)
      - Inaugural, 1964-1976, (3 folders) (Box 387)
      - Miscellany, 1978-1980, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany (Box 388)
      - Civil Service
        - Adinolfi, Joseph
        - Daly, Roy
        - New London, Conn., wage board
      - Concentrated Employment Program
      - Education
      - Fermont Division
      - Groton sewer, Lois Jones
      - Heating oil cost, (2 folders) (Box 389)
      - Housing and Urban Development and Interior-Gurski farm, Brookfield
      - Housing and Urban Development and Treasury-St. Raphael and St. Mary's hospitals
      - Office of Economic Opportunity
      - Saye and Sele, Lord
      - Miscellany, 1972-1978
  - Legislative file (Box 390)
    - Appropriations Committee
      - Agriculture Department, 1968, Mar.-1980, Oct., (3 folders)
      - Commerce Department, 1975, Sept-1980, July, (2 folders)
      - Defense Department
        - 1967, Feb.-1970, Apr., (5 folders)
        - 1970, May-1977, July, (8 folders) (Box 391)
        - 1977, July-1980, Oct., (8 folders) (Box 392)
      - Housing and Urban Development, 1967, Dec.-1980, Nov., (3 folders) (Box 393)
      - Interior Department, 1968, Apr.-1980, Sept., (4 folders)
      - District of Columbia, 1969, Sept.
      - Health, Education, and Welfare Department
        - 1969, Jan.-1970, Aug., (2 folders)
        - 1976, Jan.-1977, Dec., (9 folders) (Box 394)
        - 1978, Jan.-1979, Dec., (6 folders) (Box 395)
        - 1980, Jan.-Nov. (Box 396)
      - Legislative, 1969, Mar.-1978, July
      - State Department, Justice Department, and Judiciary, 1968, Jan.-1980, July, (2 folders)